const questions = [
	{
		question: "What's the maximum round time in standard competetive CS:GO2?",
		optionA: "2 minutes",
		optionB: "1 minute and 55 seconds", // Correct
		optionC: "1 minute and 45 seconds",
		optionD: "1 minute and 30 seconds",
		correctOption: "optionB",
	},
	{
		question: "What is the name of the bombsites on Mirage?",
		optionA: "Mid & Top-Mid",
		optionB: "A & C",
		optionC: "A & B", // Correct
		optionD: "B & C",
		correctOption: "optionC",
	},
	{
		question: "How many players are there on each team?",
		optionA: "8",
		optionB: "7",
		optionC: "6",
		optionD: "5", // Correct
		correctOption: "optionD",
	},
	{
		question: "How long does it take to defuse a bomb with a kit?",
		optionA: "10 seconds",
		optionB: "8 seconds",
		optionC: "5 seconds", // Correct
		optionD: "3 seconds",
		correctOption: "optionC",
	},
	{
		question: "Which rifle has the highest armor penetration?",
		optionA: "FAMAS",
		optionB: "AK-47",
		optionC: "AWP", // Correct
		optionD: "M4A4",
		correctOption: "optionC",
	},
	{
		question: "Which grenade can extinguish a molotov?",
		optionA: "Smoke", // Correct
		optionB: "HE Grenade",
		optionC: "Flashbang",
		optionD: "Decoy",
		correctOption: "optionA",
	},
	{
		question: "How much does a Zeus cost?",
		optionA: "500",
		optionB: "400",
		optionC: "300",
		optionD: "200", // Correct
		correctOption: "optionD",
	},
	{
		question: "Which map has the fastest rotation time between both bombsites?",
		optionA: "Ancient",
		optionB: "Dust II",
		optionC: "Nuke", // Correct
		optionD: "Anubis",
		correctOption: "optionC",
	},
	{
		question: "What is the cost of firing a single M249 bullet?",
		optionA: "17", // Correct
		optionB: "15",
		optionC: "12",
		optionD: "10",
		correctOption: "optionA",
	},
	{
		question: "What is the maximum round loss bonus?",
		optionA: "$3500",
		optionB: "$3400", // Correct
		optionC: "$3300",
		optionD: "$3200",
		correctOption: "optionB",
	}
]